

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript Sass, Less, Stylus Pug BEM Webpack, gulp, grunt

CONTACT

ahmed.guseynov.23@gmail.com guseynov.github.io

LOCATION

St. Petersburg, Russia (UTC +3)

AHMED GUSEYNOV

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I've been working as a frontend engineer for more than three years and now I'm searching for a position that would allow me to grow as a professional, use the latest technologies and techniques. Preferably I would love to participate in construction and maintenance of a modern, complex single page application. I write semantic HTML5 markup, use CSS3 techniques for implementing complex responsive designs and animations, build pixel-perfect pages and use JavaScript with popular libraries to create fast, functional and dynamic applications. I have no working experience with React, but I'm currently learning React/Redux stack and willing to gain experience. In my workflow I use npm modules, Git for version control, Pug as a template engine, Stylus, SASS or LESS as style preprocessors, BEM methodology as a naming convention, React as the main JS library and Gulp or Webpack for generating the final product.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

Netrika | June 2017 to November 2018

At Netrika I was dealing with updating and upgrading existing websites, sometimes making some relatively small projects from scratch. It was hard to grow professionally while working there, which is important for me, so I decided to quit.

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

RoyalMark | March 2015 to May 2017

At RoyalMark most of my projects were landing pages. There I usually created responsive pixel perfect web-pages using design mockups, made them interactive and capable of sending and receiving necessary information using APIs of the server.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Herzen State University | 2013 - 2017